englishanyone.com 2019-08-03

# Privacy Policy - EnglishAnyone.com - Become a Confident, Fluent English Speaker with the World's #1 English Fluency Guide

### **Privacy Policy  
**

**Company Information**

Company Name:    EnglishAnyone.com  
Address:    1216 E. Madison Park, Chicago, IL 60615  
Country:    United States  
Controller:    Drew Badger  
Website:    EnglishAnyone.com  
Support Email Address: support@englishanyone.com **  
**

**Website Services and Links**

Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.

Third party Web service providers, like Google or Facebook, may collect personal data about our visitors to ensure better service and product quality. See details below in Third Party Service Providers.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

Whenever you opt-in to receive free information and/or you purchase something from us, by webpage or email, you are added to an email list. This is so we can continue to inform you about purchases and provide updates and support.

**You may unsubscribe from any list at any time – a link to unsubscribe can be found at the bottom of every email we send. You can also unsubscribe by sending an email to info@englishanyone.com.**

When subscribing to our email lists and newsletters, your information is **not** shared with third parties, and you will only be contacted when we have something we believe will be of value to you.

**Use of Cookies (Tracking)  **

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our service.

We may automatically log personal data and we may link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

**Use of Site & Collecting Personal Information**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data, identifiers (such as credit card details, Website passwords).

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

a) unauthorized access  
b) improper use or disclosure  
c) unauthorized modification  
d) unlawful destruction or accidental loss

You may receive information about the kind of information we have for you by sending an email to info@englishanyone.com.

You may also request deletion of your personal information at any time.

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

Summary use of your data, to:

  * Provide you access to our products and service (paid and free)
  * Notify you about changes to our policies, services and products
  * Provide you with specific customer support
  * Analyze and improve our services and products
  * Monitor the usage of our various sites and blog
  * Detect, prevent and resolve technical issues
  * Provide you with news, special offers and general information about other products and services that are similar to those that you have already purchased or inquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information
  * Provide you can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us.

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our homepage, or at those sites on our Website where we collect personal data.

**Third Party Service Providers**  
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our service to you (“Service Providers”), to provide our service on our behalf, to perform related services or to assist us in analyzing how our products and service are used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Google Analytics**  
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

**Google AdWords**  
Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

**Facebook**  
Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc. You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact support at info@englishanyone.com.
